mycitymychoice.com 2017-12-19

# Privacy Policy | MyCityMyChoice

**PRIVACY POLICY** – Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site (no personally identifiable information). The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes, and lets me know what pages and information are useful and helpful to visitors, which helps me to provide more of the type of content that my visitors are interested in.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Where necessary, this site uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Controlling Your Privacy** **  
**  
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

**Special Note About Google Advertising**

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google’s cookie usage [by visiting this page.](http://www.google.ca/policies/privacy/ "Google Policies") As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

**What is the DoubleClick DART cookie?**

The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.[ Users and visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting this link and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) **  
**  
**Ad Settings** ****

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/ "Google Preferences"). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

Some third-party advertisers used by Google may use a different cookie. You may opt out of most third-party advertising cookies by [following this link and visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), or; [by visiting this Consumers page to opt out of all advertising cookies](http://www.evidon.com/consumers/profile_manager#tab3).

**Contact Information**

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be [directed to us](http://mycitymychoice.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us") for further clarification.

**DISCLAIMER**

This website is a personal endeavour to provide discussion, help and information for others. This site may from time-to-time display advertising or sponsorship, both paid and free. Any product endorsements which have paid compensation will be identified as such.

All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third party ad network. Advertisements are identified by the advertising network and where available, links are shown in the privacy policy to opt out of advertising cookies.
